[
    {
        "question": "Ic <em>(fremman)</em> #### gu&thorn;e - I make war",
        "correctAnswer": "fremme",
        "explanation":"Here 'fremman' is in the first person singular form because the subject is 'I'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "&THORN;u <em>(nerian)</em> #### &thorn;a cildras - You save the children",
        "correctAnswer": "nerest",
        "explanation":"Here 'nerian' is in the second person singular form because the subject is 'You",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He minum l&aelig;rum <em>(hieran)</em> #### - He listens to my teachings",
        "correctAnswer": "hier&thorn;",
        "explanation":"Here 'hieran' is in the third person singular form because the subject is 'He'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "We <em>(t&aelig;can)</em> #### Eald Englisc on &thorn;&aelig;m minstere - We teach Old English in the monastery",
        "correctAnswer": "tǣca&thorn;",
        "explanation":"Here 't&aelig;can' is in the first person plural form as the subject is 'We'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie hergia&thorn; and to scipe <em>(l&aelig;dan)</em> #### - they harry and carry off the plunder to their ships",
        "correctAnswer": "l&aelig;da&thorn;",
        "explanation":"Here 'l&aelig;dan' is in the third person plural form as the subject is 'They'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic <em>(sendan)</em> #### &aelig;rendracan to minum hlaforde - I sent a messenger to my lord",
        "correctAnswer": "sende",
        "explanation":"Here 'sendan' is in the first person singular past form because the subject is 'I'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgensteorran &eth;e &thorn; o&eth;re naman &aelig;fensteorra nemnan <em>(hieran)</em> #### - the morning star which we hear called evening star by another name",
        "correctAnswer": "hierdest",
        "explanation":"Here 'hieran' is in the first person singular past form because the subject is 'We",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie halig God <em>(nerian)</em> #### - They are saved by holy God",
        "correctAnswer": "neredon",
        "explanation":"Here 'nerian' is in the third person plural past form because the subject is 'They'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "We <em>(fremman)</em> #### swa and Frean hyrde - We did so and obeyed the lord",
        "correctAnswer": "fremedon",
        "explanation":"Here 'fremman' is in the first person singular past form because the subject is 'We",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Heo <em>(t&aelig;can)</em> #### us sprecan leden - She taught us to speak Latin",
        "correctAnswer": "t&aelig;hte",
        "explanation":"Here 't&aelig;can' is in the third person singular past form because the subject is 'She'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie <em>(feran)</em> #### ofer s&aelig; - They go overseas",
        "correctAnswer": "fera&thorn;",
        "explanation":"Here 'feran' is in the third person plural form because the subject is 'They'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hie <em>(feran)</em> #### to Rome - They went to Rome",
        "correctAnswer": "ferdon",
        "explanation":"Here 'feran' is in the third person plural past form because the subject is 'They'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "&THORN;a <em>(sendan)</em> #### se cyning to &thorn;am flotan Leofsig ealdorman — Then the king sent Alderman Leofsig to the fleet",
        "correctAnswer": "sende",
        "explanation":"Here 'sendan' is in the third person singular past form because the subject is 'The King'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Wyrd oft <em>(nerian)</em> #### unfægne eorl &thorn;onne his ellen deah - Fate often saves a man not fated to die",
        "correctAnswer": "nere&eth;",
        "explanation":"Here 'nerian' is in the third person singular form because the subject is 'Wyrd'",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic <em>(hieran)</em> #### &thorn;u - I hear you",
        "correctAnswer": "hiere",
        "explanation":"Here 'hieran' is in the first person singular form because the subject is 'I'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ic <em>(l&aelig;dan)</em> #### &thorn;one micel here - I led the great army",
        "correctAnswer": "l&aelig;dde",
        "explanation":"Here 'l&aelig;dan' is in the first person singular past form because the subject is 'I'",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    }
]



